=============================================================

100% free spanish lessons

-------------

Our Privacy Policy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  
  
Anonymous Data We Collect   
  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to track usage and traffic patterns so that we can better design our website. When you visit this Site, certain kinds of non-personal information, such as your IP address, any website that referred you to us, your browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site’s operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the Site. This information is used by a 3rd party (Google Analytics) to provide us with statistics about site usage. Google Analytics only has access to fully anonymous data and does not share this data with any other 3rd parties.   
  
What we do not collect   
  
We do not collect any personally identifiable information (PII) about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, such as by requesting information from us or emailing us. We do not sell, rent, lease or share information about you with any third parties.Cookies Cookies are used on this website mainly to analyze our website traffic, to show ads or to measure the success rates of advertising. 

Cookies  

Our websites make use of so-called cookies. Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer by our websites, while you’re visiting them. The files contain specific, user-related information. Cookies allow us to understand how often and how many people use our websites and to offer services in a more customized manner. We use session cookies, which temporarily store information for the duration of your visit to one of our websites. Session cookies are automatically deleted at the end of your visit. We also use permanent cookies in order to store information about users who are frequent visitors to one or more of our sites. The purpose of using these cookies is to provide you with optimum user guidance and also to help us recognise you when you return, so that we can offer you maximum variety and new content. The content of a permanent cookie is restricted to an identification number. Names, IP addresses, etc. are not stored, nor do we construct individual profiles of your usage behaviour. It is possible to use our services without cookies. You can also delete cookies from the hard disc of your computer at any time. In that case, however, you might not be able to benefit from the full potential of the functions on the websites. 

You can switch off the use of cookies for our website or in general in the settings of your Internet browser. You can find out how this functions from the website of your Internet browser supplier. For Microsoft Edge you can find the relevant instructions at [View cookies in Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/view-cookies-in-microsoft-edge-a7d95376-f2cd-8e4a-25dc-1de753474879#:%7E:text=Open%20Microsoft%20Edge%20and%20then,all%20cookies%20and%20site%20data), for Firefox at [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/block-websites-storing-cookies-site-data-firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/block-websites-storing-cookies-site-data-firefox), for Apple Safari at [https://help.apple.com/safari/mac/8.0/en.lproj/sfri11471.html](https://help.apple.com/safari/mac/8.0/en.lproj/sfri11471.html) and for Google Chrome at [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=e](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)[n](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en). 

Please note that deactivating cookies will mean that a number of functionalities on the website may no longer operate as intended. 

Privacy policy for the use of Google Analytics 

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how you use the site. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website in order to compile reports on website activity for the website operator and to provide other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. The IP address transferred by your browser within the scope of Google Analytics will not be combined with other data from Google. You may prevent the saving of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can prevent the data captured by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) from being captured and processed by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link : [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Further information on the use of the data and privacy policy at Google Analytics is available at [https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) or [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)  
  
Privacy Policy for the use of Google Adsense  
  
This website uses Google AdSense to display advertisement. Provider of these services are Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Adsense uses so-called "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer to analyse the use of the website. Further, Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible images). These web beacons help to process information, such as visitor traffic on this website. The information generated by cookies and web beacons about your use of this website (including your IP address) and dispatch of advertising formats is sent to and stored at a Google server in the U.S.A. Google may also transfer this information to their contractual partners. However, Google will not associate your IP address with any other data stored at Google's. You may prevent the installation of cookies by adjusting the settings of your browser; however, if you do so, you may be unable to use all features of this website. By using this website you agree to the processing of the collected information by Google, according to the above mentioned purpose. You can learn more about  Google Adsense privacy policy at:  [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). You can opt-out of Ads personalization at: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/)  

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
  
We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time. You should visit this page periodically to review our current Privacy Policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information. 

Last update: April 28, 2024

* Learn Spanish for Beginners
    ---------------------------

Copyright © 2015 [studyspanishlanguage.org](https://www.studyspanishlanguage.org/). All rights reserved. Design by [templated](https://templated.co/). [PRIVACY POLICY](https://www.studyspanishlanguage.org/privacy.html)
